xyone.co.uk 2007-08-16

# Xyone - Internet Marketing Specialists

---  
Privacy Policy  
   
Use of Information.  
   
Xyone Limited ("The Company") will only use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and any other applicable legislation.  
   
The Company collects personal information from visitors to this website through your usage of this website (e.g. cookies) and when you e-mail the company your details for the purpose of registration i.e. name, postal address and e-mail address.  
   
The Company may process information collected via this website for the purposes of: providing the Company's services; answering your queries; dealing with your order(s) and account(s); and providing you with information about products and services.  
   
Please tick the appropriate box if you do not wish to receive information about:  
   
The Company's products or services  
   
Or alternatively, you may opt-out by sending the Company an e-mail at [info@xyone.co.uk](mailto:info@xyone.co.uk), calling us on 0870-9504400, or writing to the Company at the following address: Xyone Limited, Pall Mall Mews, 1st Floor Offices, 36 Pall Mall, Chorley, Lancashire PR7 2LA.  
   
The Company may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.  
   
We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam).  
   
Use of Cookies.  
   
At present the Company does not use cookies although the Company reserves the right to use cookies to identify you when you visit this Website, track your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile of your business.  
   
A cookie is a small piece of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive which enables the Company to know when you visit this website.  
   
Use of cookies also allows you as a registered user of this website to be presented with a personalised version of this website, carry out transactions and have access to information about your account.  
   
Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies may restrict your use of this Website.  
   
Disclosure.  
   
The Company does not disclose information about you or your business to any third parties unless required to do so by government bodies and law enforcement agencies.  
   
Links.  
   
This Website may contain links to other websites which are outside the Company's control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their own privacy policy.  
   
Access Right.  
   
You have a right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information held about you by the Company, please write to: Xyone Limited, Pall Mall Mews, 1st Floor Offices, 36 Pall Mall, Chorley, Lancashire PR7 2LA or e-mail to [info@xyone.co.uk](mailto:info@xyone.co.uk).
